<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<videos>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode20.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Police Lab: Criminalistics</caption>
		<desc>Criminalists in the Police Laboratory in Queens, New York are part of a multi-stage process of collecting and examining evidence.</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_Episode21.flv</link>
		<date>2/22/2013</date>
	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode20.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Police Lab: Latent Print Development Unit</caption>
		<desc>Volume 2, Episode 10 - Specially trained criminalists develop fingerprints to help identify and prosecute suspects.</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode20.flv</link>
		<date>7/6/2011</date>
	</video>
    <video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_op_bike_safety.png</image>
		<caption>Bike Safety Tips</caption>
		<desc>What are the rules and regulations of the road when it comes to riding a bicycle? The NYPD's Operation Safe Cycle wants you to know. (4:45 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/OperationSafeCycle.flv</link>
		<date>6/24/2011</date>
	</video>
    <video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_cpt_endw_galfano.png</image>
		<caption>In His Own Words</caption>
		<desc>Before losing a battle with cancer, retired Captain Barry Galfano reflected on service to the Department and the impact of 9/11 on his life. (Video by the Captains Endowment Association, 8:18 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/CptEndowmentAssocGalfano.flv</link>
		<date>6/24/2011</date>
	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode10.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Emergency Service Unit</caption>
		<desc>Episode 10 - When the public needs help, they call the police. When the police need help, they call ESU. Get a glimpse into the work of the elite NYPD Emergency Service Unit. (TRT 7:48 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode10.flv</link>
		<date>4/25/2011</date>
	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_westpointrescue.png</image>
		<caption>Cliffside Rescue at West Point</caption>
		<desc>Members of the NYPD Aviation and Emergency Service Units rescued two U.S. Military Academy cadets who became stranded in complete darkness and turbulent wind on Storm King Mountain in NY.</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/NYPDAviationWestpoint.flv</link>
		<date>3/11/2011</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_natgeotv.png</image>
		<caption>Counterterror NYC - By National Geographic</caption>
		<desc>A clip from the National Geographic documentary on NYPD anti-terror measures, culminating in the New Year's Eve countdown in Times Square. (TRT 0:30)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/natgeotv_nypd.flv</link>
		<date>2/17/2011</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode19.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD UN General Assembly</caption>
		<desc>Vol. 2, Episode 9 - The NYPD has protected visiting dignitaries and the City during the United Nations General Assembly for decades. Here, a look at some of their tactics, tried and new. (4:30)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode19.flv</link>
		<date>9/23/2010</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode18.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Anti Crime Unit (Midtown South)</caption>
		<desc>Vol. 2, Episode 8 - 'Plainclothes' officers in Midtown Manhattan talk about some of the work they do to catch criminals who steal from unsuspecting victims in the City's busiest shopping and tourist areas. (6:15)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode18.flv</link>
		<date>6/25/2010</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_prez_visit.png</image>
		<caption>POTUS TO 1PP</caption>
		<desc>President Barack Obama visited the Real Time Crime Center to thank first responders to the May 1 Times Square car bomb. He addressed members of the Department and was presented with an honorary NYPD jacket. (TRT 1:47)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/presidential_visit.flv</link>
		<date>5/13/2010</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode17.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Housing Bureau</caption>
		<desc>Vol. 2, Episode 7 - More than 400,000 New Yorkers and their guests are served by NYPD Housing police officers, who work to reduce crime and enhance the quality of life for residents of public housing. (TRT 8:20)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode17.flv</link>
		<date>2/11/2010</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode16.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Gang Division</caption>
		<desc>Volume 2, Episode 6 - Gang-motivated crime is low in New York City thanks to NYPD Gang Division officers who suppress and investigate gang activity, as well as educate others on how to identify it. (TRT 5:35 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode16.flv</link>
		<date>11/13/2009</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode15.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Transit Bureau</caption>
		<desc>Volume 2, Episode 5 - While ridership is at an all-time high, the NYC subway system is the safest it's been in history. Ride the rails with NYPD Transit police officers, and learn why. (TRT 11 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode15.flv</link>
		<date>8/7/2009</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode14.png</image>
		<caption>TRAFFIC ENFORCEMENT</caption>
		<desc>Volume 2, Episode 4 - NYPD Traffic Enforcement Agents put their lives on the double yellow line to ensure the flow of traffic and the public's safety on city streets. (TRT 7:00)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode14.flv</link>
		<date>5/12/2009</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_gala.png</image>
		<caption>A Day in the Life</caption>
		<desc>Whether off-duty or on patrol, six members of the NYPD are hailed for their heroism and humanity.</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/nypd_gala.flv</link>
		<date>3/24/2009</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_barris.png</image>
		<caption>Hudson River Rescuers</caption>
		<desc>Four of the first responders to the US Airways crash-landing in the Hudson River recall the rescue effort.</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/nypd_barris_award.flv</link>
		<date>3/24/2009</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode13.png</image>
		<caption>PLANE RESCUE IN THE HUDSON RIVER</caption>
		<desc>Volume 2, Episode 3 - The first responders to the January 15 US Airways plane crash recall the afternoon that a passenger jet landed in the Hudson River, from rescue to recovery. (TRT 8:56 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode13.flv</link>
		<date>2/20/2009</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode12.png</image>
		<caption>WHY I JOINED</caption>
		<desc>Volume 2, Episode 2 - More than 1,100 men and women graduated the Police Academy on Dec. 30. Here, veteran and rookie officers across commands discuss their reasons for selecting the NYPD as a career path. (TRT 4:17 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode12.flv</link>
		<date>12/29/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode11.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Highway Patrol Unit</caption>
		<desc>Volume 2, Episode 1 - NYPD Highway officers keep traffic moving, prevent and investigate accidents, provide dignitary escorts and cover hundreds of miles throughout the five boroughs. (TRT 7:35 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode11.flv</link>
		<date>11/20/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode9.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Police Academy</caption>
		<desc>Episode 9 - From fitness to firearms, a lot goes in to preparing New York's Finest. Featuring the July 2008 class, instructors and recruiters. (TRT 7:14 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode9.flv</link>
		<date>7/17/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_medalday.png</image>
		<caption>Police Medal Day</caption>
		<desc>Thirty-three members of the New York City Police Department are recognized with four Medals of Honor, 17 Police Combat Crosses, and 12 Medals for Valor. (TRT 8:49 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/medal_day.flv</link>
		<date>6/23/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode8.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD Domestic Violence Unit</caption>
		<desc>Episode 8 - With collaboration and compassion, NYPD domestic violence prevention officers are helping to save lives. (TRT 6:15 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode8.flv</link>
		<date>5/14/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_policememorial.png</image>
		<caption>Police Memorial Day</caption>
		<desc>Eleven members of the service are honored in a Police Memorial Day ceremony. (8:55 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/policeMemorialDay.flv</link>
		<date>5/9/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_papalvisit2008.png</image>
		<caption>The Pope Comes to New York</caption>
		<desc>A montage of moments from the New York City Police Department's security coverage during the three-day visit of Pope Benedict XVI. (4:14 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/papalVisit2008.flv</link>
		<date>4/21/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode7.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD - Episode 7</caption>
		<desc>The Bomb Squad - With extreme caution, protective suits and keen canines, these detectives defuse high-risk situations to keep the public safe. (7:00 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode7.flv</link>
		<date>3/3/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_greencloud.png</image>
		<caption>Operation Green Cloud</caption>
		<desc>An NYPD Counterterrorism Bureau investigation into the purchase of liquefied chlorine gas and its potential terrorist risk as a chemical weapon. (8:13 mins)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/operationGreenCloud.flv</link>
		<date>2/13/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode6.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD - Episode 6</caption>
		<desc>The Aviation Unit - From aerial patrols to rescues at sea, the police-pilots of the New York City Police Department rise to the occasion. (8:00 mins.)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode6.flv</link>
		<date>1/14/2008</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_dedication.png</image>
		<caption>Dedication Ceremony</caption>
		<desc>The Visitor's Entrance of One Police Plaza is dedicated to three retired detectives for their bravery and heroism on New Years Eve, 1982, when they were injured in terrorist attacks targeting Police Headquarters and nearby government buildings. Commissioner Kelly presides. (6:11 mins.)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/dedication_ceremony_12_31_07.flv</link>
		<date>12/31/2007</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode5.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD - Episode 5</caption>
		<desc>NYPD Mounted Unit - New York City Police Department horses and their officers take you through equine training and patrol in New York City. (7:19 mins.)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode5.flv</link>
		<date>11/02/2007</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode4.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD - Episode 4</caption>
		<desc>The Counter Terrorism Division - created by Police Commissioner Raymond W. Kelly in the months after 9/11, this specialized unit defeats the threat with advanced technology and active teamwork. (7:30 mins.)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode4.flv</link>
		<date>10/01/2007</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode3.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD - Episode 3</caption>
		<desc>The K9 Unit - Go on patrol and on the trail with four-legged Finest - K9 Bullitt, Scooby and and their partners show how man's best friend also serves as the protectors of the city. (6:30)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode3.flv</link>
		<date>8/06/2007</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode2.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD - Episode 2</caption>
		<desc>Law Enforcement Explorers - How the NYPD Community Affairs/Youth Services unit helps students explore careers in law enforcement, while investing in their future. (6:00)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode2.flv</link>
		<date>7/06/2007</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_episode1.png</image>
		<caption>Inside the NYPD - Episode 1</caption>
		<desc>Meet the Harbor and SCUBA Units of New York's Finest, and see them in action during Fleet Week 2007. (6:45)</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/insideNYPD_episode1.flv</link>
		<date>6/01/2007</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_lifestyle.png</image>
		<caption>Up Close with the Police Commissioner</caption>
		<desc>Police Commissioner Raymond Kelly talks about policing the city, with LXTV.</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/kelly_lifestyle_interview.flv</link>
		<date>4/1/2007</date>

	</video>
	<video>
		<image>../../images/pr/thumb_gunstop.png</image>
		<caption>Operation GUNSTOP</caption>
		<desc>The Police Commissioner's message about how you can help get illegal handguns off the street and help to save lives. For more information: 1-866-GUNSTOP (1-866-426-7867).</desc>
		<link>../../media/video/operation_gunstop.flv</link>
		<date>3/1/2007</date>

	</video>
</videos>
